You’ve been keeping me busy,
你让我无法消停
I’ll take it hot right now
我将严阵以待
Cause, i know that you want me
因为我知道你发自肺腑地
From the inside out.
想要我
You got me speechless,
你令我无言
Opening my mouth.
双唇轻动
I was keeping you secret,
我一直为你隐瞒
But the word got out.
却说漏了嘴
You’re fast, and your slow
你脚步飞快 又缓缓踱步
Like cold, and your fall
如心寒之际 消沉堕落
You’re luring me out now,
你引诱我现身
Till the walls come down.
直至堡垒坍塌
You’re yes, and you’re no
没错 你将一无所有
But I’m not letting go
但我不会放开你手
I’ll be your CONTRADICTION
我将与你为敌
CONTRADICTION
为敌
I’ll be your CONTRADICTION
我将与你为敌
You’re fast, and your slow
你脚步飞快 又缓缓踱步
Like cold, and your fall
如心寒之际 消沉堕落
You’re fast, and your slow
你脚步飞快 又缓缓踱步
You’re yes, and your no
如心寒之际 消沉堕落
But i’m not letting go
但我不会放开你手
You’re yes, and your no
没错 你将一无所有
I’ll be your CONTRADICTION
我将与你为敌